Shannonlee Gafney 07960224305 • shannongafney@gmail.com

Personal Statement:

I have excellent communication skills, being a naturally friendly and supportive person which enables me to work well with others. I take responsibility for my tasks and like to see them complete before deadlines. I am very reliable and capable of using my initiative to work alone. I am extremely reliable with excellent time management skills and work well under pressure. I am continuously developing my knowledge in all areas and always keen to learn new skills to improve my professionalism.

Key Skills

- Responsible & reliable
- Time Management & Discipline
- Team player
- Adaptable & flexible
- Computer literate
- Problem-solving skills
- Team Leading experience
- Loyalty
- Keen eye to details

Employment

Agency worker with driver hire

Title: Drivers mate and loader (temporary)

Responsible:

Working around the public collecting recycling or rubbish. Generally, tasks are completing the given route of the day. Helping the team leader with traffic control and measures so that everyone is safe.

Drivers mate helping with loading and unloading products to be sent out. Going out on route helping with deliveries.

Welshwood Mannar care home April 2020 - February 2021(part time)

Title: Cook

Responsibilities:

developing healthy and balanced meals in consultation with residents and staff.

Being aware of people's religious and cultural backgrounds and how this might impact their dietary requirements,

monitoring kitchen stocks and ordering supplies and ensuring high standards of hygiene and cleanliness are maintained.

McDonald's February 2019 – January 2021(full-time)

Title: Crewmember

Responsibilities: Preparation of food for the customers, serving customers also help them with any issues whether this order is incorrect or checking for food allergies. Sorting dated products or adding dates to products if necessary, reporting anything to my manager if necessary whether this is broken equipment or something that could put myself, a colleague and/or customer at harm also dealing with issues like this right away. Cleaning the workspaces, customer dining areas and floors of any mess and displaying wet floor signs. Dealing with money by taking off the customer and giving the correct change back. At busy times I can serve a lot of customers and mistakes can be made easy, trying to be fast and effective for each customer, so double-checking has become a habit as mistakes can happen to even the best of us.

Steeple Bay Holiday Park sessional contact

2018 - 2019 Title: Chef

Responsibilities: Preparation of food for myself and the other chefs for the next shift or on the same shift, sorting dated stock and orders of food and equipment, being the head of the kitchen as organising staff, dealing with any customer issues. Also making sure the kitchen is cleaned correctly after shifts and having the kitchen open and close at the correct times. Hygiene was a key part of every day.

RDC 2015-2018

Title: processing technician

Responsibilities:

Basic functional testing of client equipment.

Grading equipment for resale or redeployment.

Destruction of client data on all equipment via Blancco and USB functions.

Destroying hard drives when required.

Upgrading and cleaning equipment to meet our client's specification.

Complying with our IT waste process and ensuring all equipment is correctly recycled.

Clifford Thames Chelmsford February 2014

Title: IT Support Apprentice

Responsibilities: Checking server backups, following the procedure, answering calls and passing messages on accordingly. Providing IT technical support throughout the company, carrying out repairs and dealing with the user's issues as they arose. I would also build computers according to customer requirements following the company's system "SysAid" and keep them updated, writing up reports and instructions to support the rest of our engineering team in preparation for level change.

Education & Training

City & Guilds September 2014

Level 2 Award in ICT Systems and Principles: distinction (GCSE A* - C)

The College at Braintree, Colchester Institute, Braintree February 2013 to June 2013 Functional IT L1 BTEC (level 1) Business Administration

The College at Braintree, Colchester Institute, Braintree
October 2012 to February 2013
City and Guilds Employability and Personal Development L1
Emergency First Aid L1
Health and Safety in the workplace L1
Managing Personal Finance L1

St Helena School, Colchester
Jan/2008 to July/2012
English GCSE C
Maths GCSE B
Science GCSE C
Business studies GCSE C
I.T GCSE A
Textiles GCSE D

Hobbies & Interests

My interests are extreme sports and motorbikes. This has happened since I have started riding motorbikes. When I'm not being an adventurous person I enjoy sitting at my computer creating small little pieces of projects programming in c# along with fixing any of my family's or friends' technical devices. I would ideally like to be working back into these fields because I have such a strong passion and knowledge of technology.

References

Both professional and character references are available upon request.